I can't tell you how excited I am to be
لا يمكنني إخباركم كم أنا متحمس
your one and only teacher for the front end Nanodegree program.
لأكون معلمكم الوحيد لبرنامج Nanodegree للواجهة الأمامية.
This is going to be so.
سيكون هذا.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
Hi. Who are you?
أهلًا من أنت؟
I'm Richard. Did you say you're the instructor for this program?
أنا ريتشارد. هل قلت بأنك معلم هذا البرنامج؟
Well, yeah. I narrated the welcome introduction.
حسنًا، نعم. لقد سردت المقدمة الترحيبية.
Why wouldn't I be the one teaching too?
لماذا لن أكون معلمًا أنا أيضًا؟
Well, I'm teaching some of the courses.
حسنًا، أنا أدرس جزءًا من هذه الدورة التدريبية.
Wait, you're teaching?
انتظر، هل أنت تُدرِّس؟
What makes you qualified?
ما الذي جعلك مؤهلًا؟
Let's see. I've been developing on the web for gosh! Well, over a decade.
لنرى. لقد عملت على تطوير الويب، يا إلهي! حسنًا، أكثر من عقد من الزمان.
I've been teaching some of this stuff at the graduate level for several years.
لقد كنت أقوم بتدريس هذه الأشياء في مستوى الدراسات العليا لعدة سنوات.
And I actually use this stuff every single day.
وفي الواقع أستخدام هذه الأشياء بصورة يومية.
All right, well, I guess we could both teach.
حسنًا، جيد، أعتقد أن كلانا يمكنه التدريس.
The thing is that I've got this list of instructors here and I just don't see you on it.
ما في الأمر أنني حصلت على هذه القائمة التي تتضمن المعلمين هنا ولم أرَك فيها.
There's a list? Oh yeah,
هل توجد قائمة؟ أجل،
we've got a ton of great instructors.
لقد حصلنا على عدد كبير من المعلمين الرائعين.
Hey there.
أهلًا بك.
This is awkward.
هذا أمر غريب.
And who are you?
ومن أنت؟
My name is Andrew and I'm one of the other instructors here.
أُسمَّى أندرو وأنا واحد من المعلمين هنا.
Been developing on the web for a couple of
لقد عملت على تطوير الويب لمدة
years now and I've also taught at a coding bootcamp.
عامين الآن، ولقد درست كذلك في برنامج مخيم تدريب الترميز "coding bootcamp".
Oh wow.
يا إلهي،
Yeah, and that's just the two of us.
نعم، ونحن فقط اثنين من المعلمين.
We also have Mike.
معنا مايك أيضًا.
Mike has been working with the web since the early 90s.
لقد تعامل مايك مع الويب منذ أوائل التسعينيات.
There's Cameron.
وهناك كاميرون.
Cameron has a master's in education and has been building websites for years.
حصل كاميرون على ماجستير في التربية وعمل على إنشاء مواقع ويب لسنوات.
Julia.
جوليا.
And then there's James.
وبعد ذلك، هناك جيمس.
And there's the other James.
ويوجد جيمس آخر.
Okay, okay. I get it.
حسنًا، حسنًا. لقد أدركت الأمر.
You've got a nice little team there.
تعملون رفقة فريق لطيف هناك.
Look, you can come back every once in awhile.
انظر، يمكنك العودة مرة واحدة في كل لحظة.
Just because this welcome part is over,
فقط لأن هذا الجزء الترحيبي قد انتهى،
doesn't mean you have to go away forever.
لا يعني أن عليك أن الرحيل إلى الأبد.
Really? You mean that?
حقًا؟ هل تقصد ذلك؟
Of course.
بالطبع.
It's a relief.
إنها مساعدة.
I'm actually, well, I'm actually Excited for this.
أنا في الواقع، حسنًا، أنا متحمس لهذا في الواقع.
And we're excited to teach you.
ونحن متحمسون كذلك لنُعلّمك.
So welcome to the Front-End Nanodegree Program.
لذا مرحبًا بك في برنامج Nanodegree للواجهة الأمامية.
Welcome. You want to take this last one?
مرحبًا بك. تريد أن تأخذ هذا الأخير؟
Welcome. Now let's get you started on your learning journey.
مرحبًا. لنُمكِّنكم الآن من بدء رحلة التعلم الخاصة بكم.